The fearless, rebellious and extraordinary life of Alexander McQueen
McQueen is a documentary film directed by Ian Bonhôte.
Alexander McQueen's rags-to-riches story is a
modern-day fairy tale, laced with the gothic.
Mirroring the savage beauty, boldness and vivacity of his design, this documentary is an intimate revelation of McQueen's own
world, both tortured and inspired, which celebrates a radical and mesmerizing genius of profound influence.
Self, played by Bernard Arnault.
Self, played by Joseph Bennett.
Self, played by Magdalena Frackowiak.
Self, played by Jodie Kidd.
Self, played by Kate Moss.
McQueen is a 2018 biographical documentary film, directed by Ian Bonhôte, written and co-directed by Peter Ettedgui, and produced by Ian
Bonhôte, Andee Ryder, Nick Taussig, and Paul Van Carter under the banner of Misfits Entertainment, and Salon Pictures.
The documentary is based on the life and career of
British fashion designer Alexander McQueen.